let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "How many bones are in the body?",
        answer: "C. 206",
        options: [
            "A. 210",
            "B. 215",
            "C. 206",
            "D. 200"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a function of the digestive tract?",
        answer: "B. To perform gas exchange",
        options: [
            "A. To enzymatically break down food",
            "B. To perform gas exchange",
            "C. To absorb nutrients into the blood",
            "D. To eliminate unabsorbed waste"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which anatomical directional term refers to a body part being located toward the front of the body?",
        answer: "C. Anterior",
        options: [
            "A. Lateral",
            "B. Superior",
            "C. Anterior",
            "D. Posterior"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Where is Vitamin K created in the body?",
        answer: "C. Large intestine",
        options: [
            "A. Liver",
            "B. Lungs",
            "C. Large intestine",
            "D. Gall bladder"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is erythropoiesis?",
        answer: "A. Red Blood cell formation",
        options: [
            "A. Red Blood cell formation",
            "B. White blood cell formation",
            "C. The destruction of red blood cells",
            "D. The destruction of white blood cells"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "A person who has torn their vestus lateralis muscle will need which of the following?",
        answer: "B. A cane or crutches",
        options: [
            "A. An arm sling",
            "B. A cane or crutches",
            "C. A rib support brace",
            "D. A neck brace"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which is a steroid hormone?",
        answer: "D. Estrogen",
        options: [
            "A. Insulin",
            "B. Calcitonin",
            "C. Adrenaline",
            "D. Estrogen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which pair of hormones regulates blood calcium homeostasis?",
        answer: "B. Parathyroid hormone and calcitonin",
        options: [
            "A. Thyroid hormone and calcitonin",
            "B. Parathyroid hormone and calcitonin",
            "C. Insulin and glucagon",
            "D. Adrenaline and noradrenaline"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What type of hormones are follicle-stimulating hormone, thyroid-stimulating hormone, and luteinizing hormone?",
        answer: "A. Tropic",
        options: [
            "A. Tropic",
            "B. Secondary",
            "C. Steroid",
            "D. Adrenal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which statement is correct?",
        answer: "B. The ventral cavity includes the thoracic and abdominopelvic cavities",
        options: [
            "A. The dorsal cavity includes the thoracic and spinal cavities",
            "B. The ventral cavity includes the thoracic and abdominopelvic cavities",
            "C. The dorsal cavity includes the spinal and abdominopelvic cavities",
            "D. The ventral cavity includes the cranial and spinal cavities"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "What is the function of cyclic adenosine monophosphate (cAMP)?",
        answer: "C. Serves as a secondary messenger",
        options: [
            "A. Is the part of the cell membrane",
            "B. Provides energy for the cell",
            "C. Serves as a secondary messenger",
            "D. Is an endocrine hormone"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Which organ within the digestive system is a site of both mechanical and chemical digestion?",
        answer: "C. Stomach",
        options: [
            "A. Esophagus",
            "B. Small intestine",
            "C. Stomach",
            "D. Large intestine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What is the most widely distributed type of sweat gland?",
        answer: "C. Eccrine",
        options: [
            "A. Apocrine",
            "B. Endocrine",
            "C. Eccrine",
            "D. Submucosal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which blood vessel returns blood from the systemic circuit to the heart?",
        answer: "D. 31",
        options: [
            "A. Coronary sinus",
            "B. Aorta",
            "C. Superior Vena Cava",
            "D. Pulmonary vein"
        ]
    },
] 